Guide to the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees, Local 1930 Records WAG.040
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; membership roster, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; Grievances, 1969-1975 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; Grievances and arbitrations, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; NYPL, Schomburg Center of Research in Black Culture; Diana Lachatanere arbitration case, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Arbitration; AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; NYPL; Diana Lachatanere, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; Grievances and arbitrations, 1982-1984 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library Association Legislation Committee; NYPL: correspondence, legislation, memos, 1972-1980 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; Agency shop materials, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1986-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; members' problems and questions, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; members' problems and questions, 1985-1988 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- 'The Library Lions(f/k/a The NYPL Staff Bulletin);' newsletter; The New York Lions Staff Association, 1926-941 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; Questionnaire regarding benefits for part-time employees, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; executive board minutes, 1978-1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; executive board minutes, 1983-1985 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; executive board minutes, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; Membership meetings minutes, 1978-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; Membership meetings minutes, 1982-1987 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- New York Public Library News; Friends of the NYPL, 1983-1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- AFSCME; booklets: officers manuals, drug treatment, OSHA, women, 1980;1981; 1986; undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO conference; memos, correspondence, registrations, flyers, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- AFSCME,Locals 3090 and 2626; Los Angeles; sample contracts, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- AFSCME, DC 37, various locals; proposed resolutions, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Correspondence; general, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Correspondence; general, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Correspondence; general, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Robert Fay; New York Public Library; correspondence, memos, employment reviews, 1984-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- AFSCME, DC 37; New York Public Library; Health and Security Plan, 1981-1985 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Local 1930; New York Public Library; Central building cafeteria closing; Labor management meeting, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- New York Library Guild Local 1930; Nicaragua Libray fund raising; correspondence, publicity, notes, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; protesting nuclear shipments through New York; correspondence, flyers, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Other library strikes: newspaper clippings, flyers, correspondence, sample contracts, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Newspaper clippings, newsletters, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Local 1930; "Retirement incentive bill"; correspondence, law codes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Workers' compensation; brochures, memos, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; General correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; General correspondence, 1967-1972 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; Grievances, arbitrations, 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; CID grievance and arbitration decision, 1980-1981 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1980-1984 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances; FICA deductions, 1958; 1979-1982 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1980-1982 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; grievances and arbitrations, 1980-1983 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- New York Public Library Staff Association Newsletter, 1935; 1938 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- New York Public Library; bulding and funding problems, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- General Library and Museum of Performing Arts @ Lincoln Center, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; disciplinary hearings and terminations (Box 12)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Repository permission is required for access. Please contact Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Archives, tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630.
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; correspondence; Marion Porro; newspaper clippings; flyers; memos; contract negotiations; Edith Rees, Early history: union to NYPL (Box 13)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; collective bargaining negotiations; correspondence; memos; flyers; newspaper clippings; union publications (Box 14)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library; correspondence, contract negotiations, grievances, union proposals, finances, memos (Box 15)
- AFSCME, DC 37, Local 1930; New York Public Library: Posters (Oversize), undated (Flat-file Top of FFC: 1-4)